A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1924-1939 FA308
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1929
  - Fiji, 1929; 1929/419
    - Fiji - Hookworm, 1929; 1929/419.H
      - Fiji, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 210)
  - Guyana, 1929; 1929/423
    - British Guiana, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 211)
  - Belize, 1929; 1929/425
    - Belize - Yellow Fever, 1929; 1929/425.O
      - British Honduras, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 211)
  - Canada, 1929; 1929/427
    - Canada - (A-L), 1929 (Box 25, Folder 211)
    - Canada - (M-Z) - Newfoundland - Nova Scotia, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 212)
    - Canada - Nursing, 1929; 1929/427.C
      - Canada, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 212)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1929; 1929/427.E
      - Canada, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 213)
    - Canada - Public Health Education, 1929; 1929/427.L
      - Canada - British Columbia - Quebec, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 214)
    - Canada - Social Sciences, 1929; 1929/427.S
      - Canada - McGill University, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 214)
  - Jamaica, 1929; 1929/437
    - Jamaica - (A-Z), 1929 (Box 26, Folder 215)
    - Jamaica - Hookworm, 1929; 1929/437.H
      - Jamaica, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 216)
    - Jamaica - Malaria, 1929; 1929/437.I
      - Jamaica - Boyd, Mark F., 1929 (Box 26, Folder 217)
      - Jamaica - Carley, Paul S. - Howard H. H. - Reports, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 218)
      - Jamaica - Washburn, B. E., 1929 (Box 26, Folder 218)
    - Jamaica - Health Services, 1929; 1929/437.K
      - Jamaica, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 218)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, 1929; 1929/446
    - St. Kitts, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 219)
  - St. Lucia, 1929; 1929/457
    - St. Lucia, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 219)
  - Ceylon, 1929; 1929/462
    - Ceylon - Malaria, 1929; 1929/462.I
      - Ceylon, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 219)
      - RUS-6 Russell, Paul F. "Ceylon - Anti-malaria Activities With Which RF is Associated - Report", 1929 (Box 554, Folder 3722)
    - Ceylon - Public Health Demonstrations, 1929; 1929/462.J
      - Ceylon, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 219)
  - India, 1929; 1929/464
    - India - (A-Z), 1929 (Box 27, Folder 220)
    - India - Madras - Health, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 221)
    - India - Nursing, 1929; 1929/464.C
      - India, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 221)
    - India - Hookworm, 1929; 1929/464.H
      - India - Kendrick, J. T., 1929 (Box 27, Folder 222)
      - India - Kendrick, J. T. - Unnithan, P. G. G., 1929 (Box 27, Folder 223)
    - India - Public Health Demonstrations, 1929; 1929/464.J
      - India, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 223)
    - India (Mysore), 1929; 1929/464.1
      - India - (Mysore), 1929 (Box 27, Folder 224)
      - India - (Mysore), 1929 (Box 27, Folder 225)
    - India (Mysore) - Hookworm, 1929; 1929/464.1H
      - India - (Mysore), 1929 (Box 27, Folder 225)
    - India (Sawantwadi), 1929; 1929/464.4
      - Sawantwadi, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 225)
      - KEN-4 Kendrick, John F. "India - Sawantwadi: Survey of Medical and Health Conditions", 1929 (Box 554, Folder 3723)
    - India (Travancore), 1929; 1929/464.5
      - Travancore, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 225)
      - Travancore, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 225)
      - Travancore, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 225)
    - India (Travancore) - Hookworm, 1929; 1929/464.5H
      - Travancore, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 225)
    - India (Travancore) - Public Health Demonstrations, 1929; 1929/464.5J
      - Travancore, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 225)
  - Bengal/Bangladesh, 1929; 1929/466
    - Bengal, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 226)
  - Iraq, 1929; 1929/470
    - Iraq, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 226)
  - New Guinea and Papua, 1929/472
    - New Guinea and Papua - Solomon Islands, 1929; 1929/472.5
      - LAM-2 Lambert, S. M. "Poliomyclitis at Visale, Solomon Islands", 1929 (Box 554, Folder 3724)
      - STE-1 Steenson, K. R. "Solomon Islands - Diary Notes", 1929 (Box 554, Folder 3725)
    - New Guinea and Papua - Solomon Islands - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1929; 1929/472.5E
      - Solomon Islands, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 226)
  - Malaysia, 1929; 1929/473
    - RUS-1B Russell, Paul F. and Yeager, Clark H. "The Straits Settlement Rural Sanitation Survey and Campaign, Final Report, 1925-1928", 1929 (Box 554, Folder 3726)
    - Malaysia (Singapore), 1929 (Box 27, Folder 226)
    - Malaysia (Singapore), 1929 (Box 27, Folder 226)
    - Malaysia - Hookworm, 1929; 1929/473.H
      - Malaysia (Singapore), 1929 (Box 27, Folder 226)
    - Malaysia - Malaria, 1929; 1929/473.I
      - Malaysia (Singapore), 1929 (Box 27, Folder 226)
    - Malaysia - Public Health Demonstrations, 1929; 1929/473.J
      - Malaysia (Singapore), 1929 (Box 27, Folder 226)
  - Seychelles, 1929; 1929/480
    - Mauritius, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 226)
  - North Africa Region, 1929; 1929/485
    - Egypt, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 227)
    - North Africa Region - Hookworm, 1929; 1929/485.H
      - HEI-4 Heiser, Victor G. "Health and Medical Work in the Sudan", 1929 (Box 554, Folder 3727)
  - South Africa, 1929; 1929/487
    - South Africa - Social Sciences, 1929; 1929/487.S
      - South Africa, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 228)
  - France, 1929; 1929/500
    - France - Humanities and Arts, 1929; 1929/500.R
      - France, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 228)
    - France - Social Sciences, 1929; 1929/500.S
      - MER-2 Merriam, Charles E. "Social Science in Paris", 1929 (Box 554, Folder 3728)
  - Algeria, 1929; 1929/501
    - Algiers, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 228)
  - Senegal, 1929; 1929/531
    - Senegal - Yellow Fever, 1929; 1929/531.O
      - Senegal, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 228)
  - China, 1929; 1929/601
    - China - Administration, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 229)
    - China - Administration, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 230)
    - China - (A-F), 1929 (Box 28, Folder 231)
    - China - Grant, Dr. J. B., 1929 (Box 28, Folder 232)
    - China - Greene, R. S., 1929 (Box 28, Folder 233)
    - China - Greene, R. S., 1929 (Box 28, Folder 234)
    - China - Health, Ministry of, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 235)
    - China - (H-P), 1929 (Box 29, Folder 236)
    - China - Rajchman, Ludwig, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 237)
    - China - (S-Y), 1929 (Box 29, Folder 238)
    - China - Medical Sciences, 1929; 1929/601.A
      - China - (C-Y), 1929 (Box 29, Folder 239)
    - China - Nursing, 1929; 1929/601.C
      - China - Shih, Mary, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 239)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1929; 1929/601.E
      - China - (C-Y), 1929 (Box 29, Folder 240)
    - China - Public Health Demonstrations, 1929; 1929/601.J
      - China, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 240)
    - China - Public Health Education, 1929; 1929/601.L
      - China, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 240)
  - Japan, 1929; 1929/609
    - Japan, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 241)
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1929; 1929/609.E
      - Japan - (A-Z), 1929 (Box 29, Folder 241)
  - Thailand, 1929; 1929/617
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1929; 1929/617.E
      - Siam (Thailand) - Atirekasar, Sa-ing, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 242)
      - Siam (Thailand) - (B-Z), 1929 (Box 29, Folder 243)
  - Holland, 1929; 1929/650
    - Netherlands, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 243)
    - Netherlands, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 243)
    - Netherlands, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 243)
    - Holland - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1929; 1929/650.D
      - Netherlands, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 243)
    - Holland - Yellow Fever, 1929; 1929/650.O
      - Netherlands, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 243)
  - Sumatra/Dutch East Indies, 1929; 1929/657
    - Dutch East Indies, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 243)
  - Europe, 1929; 1929/700
    - Europe - (A-L), 1929 (Box 29, Folder 244)
    - Europe - (M-S), 1929 (Box 30, Folder 245)
    - Europe, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 246)
    - Europe, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 246)
    - Europe - Medical Sciences, 1929; 1929/700.A
      - Europe, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 246)
    - Europe - Humanities and Arts, 1929; 1929/700.R
      - Europe, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 246)
  - Ethiopia, 1929; 1929/701
    - Ethiopia, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 247)
  - Austria, 1929; 1929/705
    - Austria, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 247)
  - Belgium, 1929; 1929/707
    - Belgium, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 247)
  - Yugoslavia, 1929; 1929/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 247)
    - Yugoslavia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1929; 1929/710.E
      - Yugoslavia - (A-Z), 1929 (Box 30, Folder 248)
  - Bulgaria, 1929; 1929/711
    - Bulgaria, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 248)
    - Bulgaria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1929; 1929/711.E
      - Bulgaria - (A-Z), 1929 (Box 30, Folder 248)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1929; 1929/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 249)
  - Estonia, 1929; 1929/714
    - Estonia, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 249)
  - Germany, 1929; 1929/717
    - Germany - (A-M), 1929 (Box 30, Folder 249)
    - Germany - (A-Z), 1929 (Box 30, Folder 251)
    - Germany - Medical Sciences, 1929; 1929/717.A
      - Germany, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 250)
    - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1929; 1929/717.E
      - Germany - (A-Z), 1929 (Box 30, Folder 251)
  - Hungary, 1929; 1929/750
    - Hungary, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 251)
    - Hungary - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1929; 1929/750.E
      - Hungary - (A-Z), 1929 (Box 30, Folder 251)
  - Italy, 1929; 1929/751
    - Italy - Malaria, 1929; 1929/751.I
      - Italy - Hackett, Lewis W., 1929 (Box 30, Folder 252)
  - Norway, 1929; 1929/767
    - Norway - Public Health Demonstrations, 1929; 1929/767.J
      - Norway, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 252)
  - Portugal, 1929; 1929/773
    - Portugal, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 252)
  - Romania, 1929; 1929/783
    - Romania - (A-Z), 1929 (Box 31, Folder 253)
  - Finland, 1929/787
    - Finland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1929; 1929/787.E
      - Finland, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 253)
  - Poland, 1929; 1929/789
    - Poland - (A-Z), 1929 (Box 31, Folder 254)
  - Sweden, 1929; 1929/800
    - Sweden - (A-Z), 1929 (Box 31, Folder 254)
    - Sweden - Medical Sciences, 1929; 1929/800.A
      - Sweden, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 254)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1929; 1929/800.E
      - Sweden, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 254)
  - Turkey, 1929; 1929/805
    - Turkey, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 254)
    - Turkey - Nursing, 1929; 1929/805.C
      - Turkey, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 255)
  - Cyprus, 1929; 1929/809
    - Cyprus, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 255)
  - Syria, 1929; 1929/833
    - Syria, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 255)
    - Syria - Nursing, 1929; 1929/833.C
      - (Lebanon), 1929 (Box 31, Folder 255)
- General Correspondence, 1930
  - International, 1930; 1930/100
    - (C-M), 1930 (Box 31, Folder 256)
    - (M-V), 1930 (Box 31, Folder 257)
    - (C-V), 1930 (Box 31, Folder 258)
    - (H-S), 1930 (Box 31, Folder 259)
    - International - Yellow Fever, 1930; 1930/100.O
      - Yellow Fever, 1930 (Box 31, Folder 260)
    - International - Tuberculosis, 1930; 1930/100.T
      - Tuberculosis Program, 1930 (Box 31, Folder 261)
  - United States, 1930; 1930/200
    - United States - (A-C), 1930 (Box 31, Folder 262)
    - United States - (C-H), 1930 (Box 32, Folder 263)
    - United States - (I-M), 1930 (Box 32, Folder 264)
    - United States - (N-Z), 1930 (Box 32, Folder 265)
    - United States - White House Conference - Ferrell, John A., 1930 (Box 32, Folder 266)
    - United States - White House Conference - Ferrell, John A., 1930 (Box 32, Folder 267)
    - United States - White House Conference - Ferrell, John A., 1930 (Box 32, Folder 268)
    - United States - White House Conference - Ferrell, John A., 1930 (Box 32, Folder 269)
    - United States - White House Conference - (A-L), 1930 (Box 33, Folder 270)
    - United States - White House Conference - (M-Z), 1930 (Box 33, Folder 271)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1930; 1930/200.A
      - United States, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 272)
    - United States - Nursing, 1930; 1930/200.C
      - United States, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 272)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/200.E
      - United States - Fellowship Inquiries - (A-S), 1930 (Box 33, Folder 272)
      - United States - Fellowship Inquiries - (T-Z), 1930 (Box 33, Folder 273)
    - United States - Health Services, 1930; 1930/200.K
      - United States, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 273)
    - United States - Public Health Education, 1930; 1930/200.L
      - Cincinnati Institute, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 274)
      - Cincinnati Institute - (M-Y), 1930 (Box 33, Folder 275)
    - United States - Yellow Fever, 1930; 1930/200.O
      - United States, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 275)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1930; 1930/200.R
      - United States, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 275)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1930; 1930/200.S
      - United States, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 275)
  - Alabama, 1930; 1930/201
    - Alabama - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/201.E
      - Alabama - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 33, Folder 276)
  - Arizona, 1930; 1930/203
    - Arizona - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 277)
    - Arizona - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 278)
    - Arizona - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 279)
    - Arizona - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 280)
    - Arizona - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/203.E
      - Arizona - Rider, Jane H., 1930 (Box 34, Folder 280)
  - Arkansas, 1930; 1930/204
    - Arkansas - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 281)
    - Arkansas - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 282)
    - Arkansas - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/204.E
      - Arkansas - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 34, Folder 283)
  - California, 1930; 1930/205
    - California - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 284)
    - California - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 285)
    - California - (A-L), 1930 (Box 34, Folder 286)
    - California - (P-Z), 1930 (Box 34, Folder 287)
  - Colorado, 1930; 1930/207
    - Colorado - State Board of Health - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 35, Folder 288)
    - Colorado - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/207.E
      - Colorado, 1930 (Box 35, Folder 288)
  - Florida, 1930; 1930/211
    - Florida - State Board of Health - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 35, Folder 289)
    - Florida - Malaria, 1930; 1930/211.I
      - Florida, 1930 (Box 35, Folder 289)
  - Georgia, 1930; 1930/212
    - Georgia - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 35, Folder 290)
    - Georgia - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 35, Folder 291)
    - Georgia, 1930 (Box 35, Folder 291)
    - Georgia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/212.E
      - Georgia, 1930 (Box 35, Folder 291)
    - Georgia - Tuberculosis, 1930; 1930/212.T
      - Georgia, 1930 (Box 35, Folder 291)
  - Hawaii, 1930; 1930/214
    - Hawaii - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 35, Folder 292)
  - Idaho, 1930; 1930/215
    - Idaho - State Board of Health - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 35, Folder 292)
  - Illinois, 1930; 1930/216
    - Illinois - State Board of Health - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 35, Folder 293)
    - Illinois - University of Chicago - (A-L), 1930 (Box 35, Folder 294)
    - Illinois - University of Chicago - (M-Z), 1930 (Box 35, Folder 295)
    - Illinois - Epidemiological Investigations and Studies, 1930; 1930/216.Q
      - Illinois, 1930 (Box 35, Folder 295)
  - Indiana, 1930; 1930/217
    - Indiana - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 36, Folder 296)
  - Iowa, 1930; 1930/218
    - Iowa - State Board of Health - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 36, Folder 296)
  - Kansas, 1930; 1930/219
    - Kansas - State Board of Health - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 36, Folder 297)
  - Kentucky, 1930; 1930/220
    - Kentucky - State Board of Health - (A-D), 1930 (Box 36, Folder 298)
    - Kentucky - State Board of Health - (D-P), 1930 (Box 36, Folder 299)
    - Kentucky - State Board of Health - (R-Y), 1930 (Box 36, Folder 300)
    - Kentucky - Epidemiological Investigations and Studies, 1930; 1930/220.Q
      - Kentucky, 1930 (Box 36, Folder 300)
  - Louisiana, 1930; 1930/221
    - Louisiana - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 36, Folder 301)
    - Louisiana - State Board of Health - (K-T), 1930 (Box 36, Folder 302)
    - Louisiana - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/221.E
      - Louisiana, 1930 (Box 36, Folder 302)
  - Maine, 1930; 1930/222
    - Maine, 1930 (Box 36, Folder 303)
  - Maryland, 1930; 1930/223
    - Maryland, 1930 (Box 36, Folder 303)
  - Michigan, 1930; 1930/225
    - Michigan, 1930 (Box 36, Folder 303)
  - Minnesota, 1930; 1930/226
    - Minnesota, 1930 (Box 36, Folder 303)
  - Mississippi, 1930; 1930/227
    - Mississippi - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 37, Folder 304)
    - Mississippi - State Board of Health - Janney, John H., 1930 (Box 37, Folder 305)
    - Mississippi - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 37, Folder 306)
    - Mississippi - Malaria, 1930; 1930/227.I
      - Mississippi, 1930 (Box 37, Folder 307)
    - Mississippi - Public Health Education, 1930; 1930/227.L
      - Mississippi - Indianola - Training Station, 1930 (Box 37, Folder 307)
      - Mississippi - Indianola - Training Station, 1930 (Box 37, Folder 308)
      - Mississippi - Indianola - Training Station, 1930 (Box 37, Folder 309)
    - Mississippi - Tuberculosis, 1930; 1930/227.T
      - Mississippi, 1930 (Box 37, Folder 309)
  - Missouri, 1930; 1930/228
    - Missouri - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 37, Folder 310)
  - Montana, 1930; 1930/229
    - Montana - State Board of Health - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 38, Folder 311)
  - Nebraska, 1930; 1930/230
    - Nebraska, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 311)
  - Nevada, 1930; 1930/231
    - Nevada, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 311)
  - New Hampshire, 1930; 1930/232
    - New Hampshire, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 312)
  - New Jersey, 1930; 1930/233
    - New Jersey, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 312)
    - New Jersey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/233.E
      - New Jersey, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 312)
  - New Mexico, 1930; 1930/234
    - New Mexico, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 312)
  - North Carolina, 1930; 1930/236
    - North Carolina - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 313)
    - North Carolina - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 38, Folder 314)
    - North Carolina, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 315)
    - North Carolina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/236.E
      - North Carolina, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 315)
    - North Carolina - Humanities and Arts, 1930; 1930/236.R
      - North Carolina, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 315)
  - North Dakota, 1930; 1930/237
    - North Dakota, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 315)
    - North Dakota - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/237.E
      - North Dakota, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 315)
  - Ohio, 1930; 1930/238
    - Ohio, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 316)
    - Ohio - Epidemiological Investigations and Studies, 1930; 1930/238.Q
      - Ohio, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 316)
  - Oklahoma, 1930; 1930/239
    - Oklahoma, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 316)
  - Oregon, 1930; 1930/240
    - Oregon, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 316)
  - Pennsylvania, 1930; 1930/241
    - Pennsylvania, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 317)
    - Pennsylvania - Medical Sciences, 1930/241.A
      - Pennsylvania (Box 38, Folder 317)
  - Philippines, 1930; 1930/242
    - Philippines - Medical Sciences, 1930; 1930/242.A
      - Philippines (Box 38, Folder 317)
  - Rhode Island, 1930; 1930/244
    - Rhode Island, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 317)
  - South Carolina, 1930; 1930/246
    - South Carolina - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 318)
    - South Carolina, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 319)
    - South Carolina, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 319)
    - South Carolina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/246.E
      - South Carolina, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 319)
    - South Carolina - Public Health Education, 1930; 1930/246.L
      - South Carolina, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 319)
    - South Carolina - Yellow Fever, 1930; 1930/246.O
      - South Carolina, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 319)
  - South Dakota, 1930; 1930/247
    - South Dakota, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 320)
  - Tennessee, 1930; 1930/248
    - Tennessee - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 321)
    - Tennessee - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 322)
    - Tennessee - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 323)
    - Tennessee - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 324)
    - Tennessee - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 40, Folder 325)
    - Tennessee - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/248.E
      - Tennessee - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 40, Folder 325)
  - Texas, 1930; 1930/249
    - Texas, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 326)
  - Utah, 1930; 1930/250
    - Utah, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 326)
  - Vermont, 1930; 1930/251
    - Vermont, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 326)
  - Virginia, 1930; 1930/252
    - Virginia - State Board of Health, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 327)
    - Virginia - State Board of Health - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 40, Folder 328)
    - Virginia - Epidemiological Investigations and Studies, 1930; 1930/252.Q
      - Virginia - Albemarle County, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 329)
  - Washington, 1930; 1930/253
    - Washington, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 330)
  - West Virginia, 1930; 1930/254
    - West Virginia, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 330)
  - Wisconsin, 1930; 1930/255
    - Wisconsin, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 331)
  - Wyoming, 1930; 1930/256
    - Wyoming, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 331)
  - South America, 1930; 1930/300
    - South America, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 332)
    - South America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/300.E
      - South America, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 332)
  - Argentina, 1930; 1930/301
    - Argentina, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 332)
    - Argentina, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 332)
    - Argentina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/301.E
      - Argentina, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 332)
    - Argentina - Malaria, 1930; 1930/301.I
      - Argentina, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 332)
  - Brazil, 1930; 1930/305
    - Brazil, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 332)
    - Brazil - Yellow Fever, 1930; 1930/305.O
      - BAI-5 Bailey, Charles A. Brazil Journal, October 24-December 27, 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3730)
      - SHA-5 Shannon, Raymond C. "Brazil - Yellow Fever Mosquito Survey, Bornfim, Bahia", 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3731)
      - SOP-1 Soper, Fred L. "Brazil - Northern Zone: Report of Yellow Fever Service, January-August 1930" (Box 555, Folder 3732)
      - WIL-1 Wilson, D. Bruce "Role of Moringues in Mosquito Breeding", 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3733)
  - Chile, 1930; 1930/309
    - Chile, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 333)
    - Chile, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 333)
    - Chile - Yellow Fever, 1930; 1930/309.O
      - Chile, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 333)
  - Colombia, 1930; 1930/311
    - Colombia - Nursing, 1930; 1930/311.C
      - Colombia, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 333)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/311.E
      - Colombia, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 333)
    - Colombia - Malaria, 1930; 1930/311.I
      - Colombia, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 333)
  - Costa Rica, 1930; 1930/313
    - Costa Rica, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 334)
    - Costa Rica - Hookworm, 1930; 1930/313.H
      - Costa Rica, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 334)
    - Costa Rica - Public Health Demonstrations, 1930; 1930/313.J
      - Costa Rica, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 334)
    - Costa Rica - Health Services, 1930; 1930/313.K
      - Costa Rica, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 334)
  - Cuba, 1930; 1930/315
    - Cuba, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 334)
  - Guatemala, 1930; 1930/319
    - Guatemala, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 335)
    - ELM-3 Elmendorf, John E., Jr. "Guatemala: Hookworm Egg Count Survey", 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3734)
    - Guatemala, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 335)
    - Guatemala - Hookworm, 1930; 1930/319.H
      - Guatemala, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 335)
      - ELM-3 Elmendorf, John E., Jr. "Guatemala: Hookworm Egg Count Survey", 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3734)
    - Guatemala - Malaria, 1930; 1930/319.I
      - Guatemala, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 335)
  - Haiti, 1930; 1930/320
    - HEI-8 Heiser, Victor G. "Haiti: Health and Medical Relief", 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3735)
  - Mexico, 1930; 1930/323
    - Mexico - Carr, Henry P., 1930 (Box 41, Folder 336)
    - Mexico - Carr, Henry P., 1930 (Box 41, Folder 337)